interracu.com 2018-12-21

# FACTS

                                                                                                          Revised 10/01/2018
                                                                                                           Reviewed 10/2018
                      WHAT DOES INTERRA CREDIT UNION
FACTS                 DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
                      Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
Why?                  consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how
                      we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
                      understand what we do.
What?                 The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                      have with us. This information can include:
                       n    Social Security number and income
                       n    account balances and payment history
                       n    credit history and credit scores
                      When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this
                      notice.
How?                  All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday
                      business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’
                      personal information; the reasons Interra chooses to share; and whether you can limit this
                      sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information                  Does Interra share?         Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes—
such as to process your transactions, maintain
                                                                        Yes                              No
your account(s), respond to court orders and legal
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes—
                                                                        Yes                              No
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial companies                      Yes                              No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                        Yes                              No
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                         No                       We don't share
information about your creditworthiness
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                       No                       We don't share
Questions?            Call 574.534.2506 or 888.432.2848 or go to www.interracu.com

Page 2
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?        Interra Credit Union
                                     PO Box 727
                                     Goshen, IN 46527
What we do
How does Interra protect my personal To protect your personal information from unauthorized access
information?                         and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
                                     These measures include computer safeguards and secured files
                                     and buildings.
                                     In addition, we use “cookies” for security purposes with our online
                                     transactions and web based applications and communications.
How does Interra collect my personal We collect your personal information, for example, when you
information?                         n   open an account or apply for a loan
                                     n   make deposits or withdrawals from your account or make a wire
                                          transfer
                                     n   seek advice about your investments
                                     We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit
                                     bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
                                     Federal law gives you the right to limit only
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
                                     n   sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information
                                          about your creditworthiness
                                     n   affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                     n   sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                     State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                                     limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates                           Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                     financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                     n   Our affiliates include Members Financial Management Center, Inc.
Nonaffiliates                        Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                     financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                     n   Interra does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint marketing                      A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that
                                     together market financial products or services to you.
                                     n   Our joint marketing partners include companies offering products or
                                          services from the following categories: insurance, investments,
                                          credit cards, loans/student loans, bill pay and other electronic
                                          services.
